{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Which of the following SQL statements are helpful in database redesign?", "opta": "Correlated subqueries only", "optb": "EXISTS/NOT EXISTS expressions only", "optc": "Both of the above are helpful", "optd": "None of the above are helpful.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What SQL command can be used to delete columns from a table?", "opta": "MODIFY TABLE TableName DROP COLUMN ColumnName", "optb": "MODIFY TABLE TableName DROP ColumnName", "optc": "ALTER TABLE TableName DROP COLUMN ColumnName", "optd": "ALTER TABLE TableName DROP ColumnName", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Database redesign is not terribly difficult if the:", "opta": "database is structured.", "optb": "database is well-designed.", "optc": "database has no data.", "optd": "database is relatively small.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which SQL-92 standard SQL command can be used to change a table name?", "opta": "RENAME TABLE", "optb": "CHANGE TABLE", "optc": "ALTER TABLE", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The process of reading a database schema and producing a data model from that schema is known as:", "opta": "data modeling.", "optb": "database design.", "optc": "reverse engineering.", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Before any changes to database structure are attempted one should first:", "opta": "clearly understand the current structure and contents of the database only.", "optb": "test any changes on a test database only.", "optc": "create a complete backup of the operational database only.", "optd": "All of the above should be done.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following modifications may not succeed?", "opta": "Changing a column data type from char to date", "optb": "Changing a column data type from numeric to char", "optc": "Both of the above actions should succeed.", "optd": "Neither of the above actions will succeed.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How can you find rows that do not match some specified condition?", "opta": "EXISTS", "optb": "Double use of NOT EXISTS", "optc": "NOT EXISTS", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A regular subquery can be processed:", "opta": "from the top down.", "optb": "from the bottom up.", "optc": "by nesting.", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What SQL command can be used to add columns to a table?", "opta": "MODIFY TABLE TableName ADD COLUMN ColumnName", "optb": "MODIFY TABLE TableName ADD ColumnName", "optc": "ALTER TABLE TableName ADD COLUMN ColumnName", "optd": "ALTER TABLE TableName ADD ColumnName", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The EXISTS keyword will be true if:", "opta": "any row in the subquery meets the condition only.", "optb": "all rows in the subquery fail the condition only.", "optc": "both of these two conditions are met.", "optd": "neither of these two conditions is met.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Changing cardinalities in a database is:", "opta": "a common database design task.", "optb": "a rare database design task, but does occur.", "optc": "a database design task that never occurs.", "optd": "is impossible to do, so a new database must be constructed and the data moved into it.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The NOT EXISTS keyword will be true if:", "opta": "any row in the subquery meets the condition.", "optb": "all rows in the subquery fail the condition.", "optc": "both of these two conditions are met.", "optd": "neither of these two conditions is met.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The data model that is produced from reverse engineering is:", "opta": "a conceptual model.", "optb": "an internal model.", "optc": "a logical model.", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To drop a column that is used as a foreign key, first:", "opta": "drop the primary key.", "optb": "drop the table containing the foreign key..", "optc": "drop the foreign key constraint.", "optd": "All of the above must be done.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What SQL command will allow you to change the table STUDENT to add the constraint named GradeCheck that states that the values of the Grade column must be greater than 0?", "opta": "ALTER TABLE STUDENT ALTER CONSTRAINT GradeCheck (Grade > 0);", "optb": "ALTER TABLE STUDENT ADD CONSTRAINT GradeCheck (Grade > 0);", "optc": "ALTER TABLE STUDENT ADD CONSTRAINT GradeCheck CHECK (Grade > 0);", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which is not true of a correlated subquery?", "opta": "EXISTS/NOT EXISTS is a form of a correlated subquery.", "optb": "The processing of the SELECT statements is nested.", "optc": "They can be used to verify functional dependencies.", "optd": "They are very similar to a regular subquery.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A tool that can help designers understand the dependencies of database structures is a:", "opta": "dependency graph.", "optb": "data model.", "optc": "graphical display.", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many copies of the database schema are typically used in the redesign process?", "opta": "One", "optb": "Two", "optc": "Three", "optd": "Four", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Because of the importance of making data model changes correctly, many professionals are ________ about using an automated process for database redesign.", "opta": "optimistic", "optb": "skeptical", "optc": "ambivalent", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}